Yu Guan Ting Thomas

front-end developer

I am a driven and highly motivated software developer with a strong background in team working and effective communication. My past experience demonstrates rapid learning abilities and adaptability across various programming languages, making me a valuable asset in dynamic IT coding environments.

thisisthomasyu@gmail.com

Johor Bahru, Malaysia

in linkedin.com/in/guan-ting-yu-88b13b267

+601120905095

- thomasfishy.netlify.app/
- github.com/ThisisFishy

EDUCATION

HD Electronic and Information EngineeringThe Hong Kong Polytechnic University

09/2018 - 03/2022

HongKong GPA: 2.98

Courses

- Object-Oriented Design And Programming
- Database System
- Computer Programming
- Intergrated Project

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technician

Tak Wa Medical Center

05/2022 - 12/2022

Macau

ORGANIZATIONS

Student Organization Sports Affairs Committee (09/2019 - 09/2021)

President

Orientation Camp Organizing Committee (09/2019 - 09/2020)

President

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Personal Website (03/2023 - Present)

• https://thomasfishy.netlify.app

CERTIFICATES

HD Electronic and Information Engineering (09/2018 - 03/2022)

https://www.acvp.hk/verification/sharelinks/abdf99d0-9364-4fa3-a4d1-0c83682aafea

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (01/2023 - 03/2023)

https://freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc950351b1-68bf -4a34-9363-d9d5ba7daad0/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

Responsive Web Design (01/2023 - 03/2023)

https://freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc950351b1-68bf-4a34-9363-d9d5ba7daad0/responsive-web-design

LANGUAGES

English

Mandarin

Professional Working Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Cantonese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

WEB3

BlockChain

NFT

Bartending